The Dalton Gang is a western film directed by Christopher Forbes.
When their brother Frank is killed by an outlaw, brothers Bob Dalton, Emmett
Dalton and Gray Dalton join their local sheriff's department.
When they are cheated by the law, they turn to crime, robbing trains and anything else
they can steal from over the course of two years in the early 1890's.
Trying to out do Jesse James, they attempt to rob two banks at
once in October of 1892, and things get ugly
Slade, played by William Adams.
Bridget McGill, played by Jezibell Anat.
Skeeter, played by Gunner Bridger.
Julia Johnson, played by Meghan Bridgers.
Bob Dalton, played by Jerry Chesser.
Grat Dalton, played by Alan Cope II.
Emmett Dalton (May 3, 1871 – July 13, 1937) was an American outlaw, train
robber and member of the Dalton Gang in the American Old West.
Part of a gang that attempted to rob two banks in Coffeyville, Kansas, on October 5, 1892, he
was the only member of five to survive, despite receiving 23 gunshot wounds.
Two of his brothers were killed.
After serving 14 years in prison for the crime, Dalton was pardoned.
He later capitalized on his notoriety, both as a writer and as an actor.
His 1918 serial story Beyond the Law was adapted as a
like-named silent film in which he played himself.
His 1931 book When the Daltons Rode was adapted after his
death as a 1940 film of the same name.